Ellen L. Lutz Papers MS177
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Human rights litigation files, 1957 -- 2004; 1986 -- 1999; MS177.004; 17.35 Linear Feet
  - Ferdinand Marcos, 1962 -- 2004; 1986 -- 1999; MS177.004.002; 13.2 Linear Feet
    - 9th Circuit en banc decision, Republic of Philippines v. Marcos, 1988; MS177.004.002.029.00017 (Box 29)
    - [Plaintiffs' motions, 9th Circuit], 1988; MS177.004.002.029.00018 (Box 29)
    - Domingo v. Marcos, 1986 -- 1989; MS177.004.002.029.00019 (Box 29)
    - [Sison / Piopongco pleadings and proceedings before 9th Circuit Court of Appeals], 1987 -- 1989; MS177.004.002.029.00020 (Box 29)
    - Philippine Blue Ribbon Committee, Oct. 25, 1989, MS177.004.002.029.00021 (Box 29)
    - Marcos case - Blue Ribbon Committee testimony, 1989; MS177.004.002.029.00022 (Box 29)
    - Hilao v. Marcos, motion to dismiss, 1990; MS177.004.002.029.00023 (Box 29)
    - Defendants motion to dismiss, 1990; MS177.004.002.029.00024 (Box 29)
    - Defendant's opposition motion, pretrial consolidation, 1990; MS177.004.002.029.00025 (Box 29)
    - [Dockets], 1990; MS177.004.002.029.00026 (Box 29)
    - Imelda Marcos documents [1 of 3], 1972 -- 1991; MS177.004.002.029.00027 (Box 29)
    - Imelda Marcos documents [2 of 3], 1976 -- 1977; MS177.004.002.029.00028 (Box 29)
    - Imelda Marcos documents [3 of 3], 1973 -- 1985; MS177.004.002.029.00029 (Box 29)
    - Documents produced by defendant [1 of 2], 1976 -- 1991; MS177.004.002.029.00030 (Box 29)
    - Documents produced by defendant [2 of 2], 1983 -- 1984; MS177.004.002.030.00001 (Box 30)
    - Sison v. Marcos - abatement [1 of 4], 1962 -- 1990; MS177.004.002.030.00002 (Box 30)
    - Sison v. Marcos - abatement [2 of 4], 1976 -- 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00003 (Box 30)
    - Sison v. Marcos - abatement [3 of 4], 1980 -- 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00004 (Box 30)
    - Sison v. Marcos - abatement [4 of 4]: Intervention, cases, authority, 1977 -- 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00005 (Box 30)
    - Misc. old Marcos files: Plaintiff's demand for jury trial, 1986; MS177.004.002.030.00006 (Box 30)
    - Misc. old Marcos files: Marcos litigation - Fall 1989, MS177.004.002.030.00007 (Box 30)
    - Misc. old Marcos files, 1987 -- 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00008 (Box 30)
    - Sison v. Marcos fundraising, 1986 -- 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00009 (Box 30)
    - [Plaintiffs' class certification], 1989 -- 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00010 (Box 30)
    - Sison v. Marcos - Real [1 of 5]: Decision of multi-district litigation panel, 1990; MS177.004.002.030.00011 (Box 30)
    - Sison v. Marcos - Real [2 of 5]: Swift's motion to consolidate cases for trial / replies, 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00012 (Box 30)
    - Sison v. Marcos - Real [3 of 5]: Motion to consolidate plaintiffs and transfer, 1990; MS177.004.002.030.00013 (Box 30)
    - Sison v. Marcos - Real [4 of 5]: Multidistrict litigation motion / response / notes, 1990; MS177.004.002.030.00014 (Box 30)
    - Sison v. Marcos - Real [5 of 5], 1990 -- 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00015 (Box 30)
    - Withdrawal notice of John T. Bartko, 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00016 (Box 30)
    - Class action: letters rogatory, 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00017 (Box 30)
    - Defendant's answers to plaintiff's complaint, 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00018 (Box 30)
    - Class action, 1989 -- 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00019 (Box 30)
    - Certification of class (Swift's case), 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00020 (Box 30)
    - Agapita Trajano's answers to defendant's first request, 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00021 (Box 30)
    - Hilao: Plaintiff's answers to interrogatory, 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00022 (Box 30)
    - Gene Chao - direct, 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00023 (Box 30)
    - Trajano judgement (against), 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00024 (Box 30)
    - Declarations, 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00025 (Box 30)
    - [Trajano appeal, 9th Circuit, appellant brief], 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00026 (Box 30)
    - [Trajano appeal, 9th Circuit, answering brief], 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00027 (Box 30)
    - Trajano - 11/12/91 to CHRON [1 of 5], 1991; MS177.004.002.030.00028 (Box 30)
    - Trajano - 11/12/91 to CHRON [2 of 5], 1991; MS177.004.002.031.00001 (Box 31)
    - Trajano - 11/12/91 to CHRON [3 of 5], 1991; MS177.004.002.031.00002 (Box 31)
    - Trajano - 11/12/91 to CHRON [4 of 5], 1991; MS177.004.002.031.00003 (Box 31)
    - Trajano - 11/12/91 to CHRON [5 of 5], 1991; MS177.004.002.031.00004 (Box 31)
    - [Trajano appeal, 9th Circuit, amicus curiae], 1991; MS177.004.002.031.00005 (Box 31)
    - Romeo T. Capulong death threat, 1991; MS177.004.002.031.00006 (Box 31)
    - Judge Real, 1991; MS177.004.002.031.00007 (Box 31)
    - [Draft briefs, memos and arguments], 1991 -- 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00008 (Box 31)
    - [Draft briefs, memos and arguments regarding Torture Victim Protection Act], 1991 -- 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00009 (Box 31)
    - Hilao appeal, volume I, 11/91 to 6/92, 1991 -- 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00010 (Box 31)
    - [Hilao appeal, 9th Circuit, brief of appellant], 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00011 (Box 31)
    - [Trajano appeal, 9th Circuit, Judge Rymer opinion], 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00012 (Box 31)
    - [Reply brief of appellant, 9th Circuit], 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00013 (Box 31)
    - [Trajano appeal, 9th Circuit], 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00014 (Box 31)
    - Marcos litigation [drafts, memos and notes], 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00015 (Box 31)
    - [Marcos victim sheets and damages notes], 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00016 (Box 31)
    - Jimmy [Piopongco testimony] - direct, 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00017 (Box 31)
    - Ely [Piopongco testimony] - direct, 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00018 (Box 31)
    - Posner - direct, 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00019 (Box 31)
    - Amelia [Sison] - direct, 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00020 (Box 31)
    - Opening argument [Sison], 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00021 (Box 31)
    - Manuel Carino, 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00022 (Box 31)
    - Trajano v. Marcos, 9th Circuit decision, 1992, MS177.004.002.031.00023 (Box 31)
    - Trajano v. Marcos - petition for writ of certiorari, 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00024 (Box 31)
    - [Trial jury selection, schedule, declassified documents and notes], 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00025 (Box 31)
    - [Hilao, 9th Circuit, record excerpts of appellant], 1992; MS177.004.002.031.00026 (Box 31)
    - Press regarding Marcos litigation, 1987 -- 1993; MS177.004.002.031.00027 (Box 31)
    - Delfin Dan Dan, class individual complaint, 1993; MS177.004.002.031.00028 (Box 31)
    - Marcos litigation, partial transcript in proceedings, opening argument, 9/15/93 and 9/9/92, 1992; MS177.004.002.032.00001 (Box 32)
    - Marcos litigation, partial transcript in proceedings, 1992; MS177.004.002.032.00002 (Box 32)
    - Marcos litigation, partial transcript in proceedings, 9/17/92, 1992; MS177.004.002.032.00003 (Box 32)
    - Marcos litigation, partial transcript in proceedings, 9/22/92, 1992; MS177.004.002.032.00004 (Box 32)
    - Marcos liability trial transcript, Sept. 1992, Volume I, MS177.004.002.032.00005 (Box 32)
    - Marcos liability trial transcript, Sept. 1992, Volume II, MS177.004.002.032.00006 (Box 32)
    - Marcos liability trial transcript, Sept. 1992, Volume III, MS177.004.002.032.00007 (Box 32)
    - Marcos liability trial transcript, Sept. 1992, Volume IV, MS177.004.002.032.00008 (Box 32)
    - Marcos liability trial transcript, Sept. 1992, Volume V, MS177.004.002.032.00009 (Box 32)
    - Marcos liability trial transcript, Sept. 1992, Volume VI, MS177.004.002.032.00010 (Box 32)
    - Marcos liability trial transcript, Sept. 1992, Volume VII, MS177.004.002.032.00011 (Box 32)
    - Marcos liability trial transcript, Sept. 1992, Volume VIII, MS177.004.002.032.00012 (Box 32)
    - Marcos liability trial transcript, Sept. 1992, Volume IX, MS177.004.002.032.00013 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence - in-house, 7/91 - 12/91, 1991; MS177.004.002.032.00014 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence - in-house, 1/92 - 6/92, 1992; MS177.004.002.032.00015 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence - in-house, 7/92 - 12/92, 1992; MS177.004.002.032.00016 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence - in-house, January 1993 -, MS177.004.002.032.00017 (Box 32)
    - Marcos, correspondence with opposing counsel - 1/91 to 8/91, 1991; MS177.004.002.032.00018 (Box 32)
    - Marcos, correspondence with opposing counsel - 9/91 to 12/91, 1991; MS177.004.002.032.00019 (Box 32)
    - Marcos, correspondence with opposing counsel - January 1993 -, MS177.004.002.032.00020 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence - co-counsel, 1991, MS177.004.002.032.00021 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence - co-counsel, 1992, MS177.004.002.032.00022 (Box 32)
    - Marcos litigation, Correspondence with co-counsel, January 1993 -, MS177.004.002.032.00023 (Box 32)
    - [Correspondence with co-counsel], 1993; MS177.004.002.032.00024 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence - Sison visa, 1991, 1991 -- 1993; MS177.004.002.032.00025 (Box 32)
    - Discovery deposition - Abrenica, 1992; MS177.004.002.032.00026 (Box 32)
    - Discovery deposition - Bernas, 1992; MS177.004.002.032.00027 (Box 32)
    - [Discovery deposition - Cohen], 1992; MS177.004.002.032.00028 (Box 32)
    - [Discovery deposition - Cohen], 1992; MS177.004.002.032.00029 (Box 32)
    - [Discovery deposition - Cohen, volume 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00001 (Box 33)
    - Discovery deposition - Sister Mariani Dimaranan, 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00002 (Box 33)
    - Discovery deposition - Felix, 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00003 (Box 33)
    - Deposition, Imelda R. Marcos, 1/14/93, 1993; MS177.004.002.033.00004 (Box 33)
    - Marcos litigation, discovery, Imelda Marcos deposition exhibits, 1993; MS177.004.002.033.00005 (Box 33)
    - Deposition, Ferdinand E. Marcos Jr., 1/15/93, 1993; MS177.004.002.033.00006 (Box 33)
    - Discovery deposition - Muego, 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00007 (Box 33)
    - Confidential deposition - Muego, 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00008 (Box 33)
    - Discovery deposition - Nonesa, 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00009 (Box 33)
    - Discovery deposition - Diane Orentlicher, 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00010 (Box 33)
    - Piopongco deposition, 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00011 (Box 33)
    - Piopongco deposition [1 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00012 (Box 33)
    - Piopongco deposition [2 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00013 (Box 33)
    - [Discovery deposition - Michael Posner], 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00014 (Box 33)
    - Discovery deposition - Purugganan, 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00015 (Box 33)
    - [Discovery deposition - Purugganan], 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00016 (Box 33)
    - Joema [Sison] deposition, 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00017 (Box 33)
    - Julie [Sison] deposition, 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00018 (Box 33)
    - [Declaration - Vizmanos], 1992; MS177.004.002.033.00019 (Box 33)
    - Index to Marcos files, 1993; MS177.004.002.033.00020 (Box 33)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 1, 1/91 - 6/91 [1 of 2], 1991; MS177.004.002.033.00021 (Box 33)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 1, 1/91 - 6/91 [2 of 2], 1991; MS177.004.002.033.00022 (Box 33)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 2, 7/91 - 9/91 [1 of 2], MS177.004.002.033.00023 (Box 33)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 2, 7/91 - 9/91 [2 of 2], MS177.004.002.033.00024 (Box 33)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 3, 10/91 - 12/91 [1 of 3], 1991; MS177.004.002.033.00025 (Box 33)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 3, 10/91 - 12/91 [2 of 3], 1991; MS177.004.002.033.00026 (Box 33)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 3, 10/91 - 12/91 [3 of 3], 1991; MS177.004.002.034.00001 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 4, 1/92 [1 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00002 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 4, 1/92 [2 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00003 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 5, 2/92 - 4/92 [1 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00004 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 5, 2/92 - 4/92 [2 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00005 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 6, 5/92 [1 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00006 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 6, 5/92 [2 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00007 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 7, 6/1/92 - 6/25/92 [1 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00008 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 7, 6/1/92 - 6/25/92 [2 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00009 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 8, 6/25/92, joint stipulation regarding discovery dispute [1 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00010 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 8, 6/25/92, joint stipulation regarding discovery dispute [2 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00011 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 9, 6/10/92 - 9/24/92 [1 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00012 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 9, 6/10/92 - 9/24/92 [2 of 2], 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00013 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 10, 10/1/92 - 10/28/92, 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00014 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 11, 11/12/92 - 12/21/92, 1992; MS177.004.002.034.00015 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 12, 1/15/93 - 5/18/93 [1 of 2], 1993; MS177.004.002.034.00016 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, Volume 12, 1/15/93 - 5/18/93 [2 of 2], 1993; MS177.004.002.034.00017 (Box 34)
    - Nolasco Buhay claim form, 1993; MS177.004.002.034.00018 (Box 34)
    - Jury instructions regarding liability, 1993; MS177.004.002.034.00019 (Box 34)
    - Press clippings, 1992 -- 1994; MS177.004.002.034.00020 (Box 34)
    - Marcos I and II, 1992 -- 1994; MS177.004.002.034.00021 (Box 34)
    - Jose Maria Sison - asylum related problems, 1993 -- 1994; MS177.004.002.034.00022 (Box 34)
    - Marcos exemplary damages trial transcript, Feb. 1994, MS177.004.002.034.00023 (Box 34)
    - [Class, 9th Circuit, plaintiffs' reply brief to US amicus curiae], 1994; MS177.004.002.034.00024 (Box 34)
    - Hilao v. Marcos regarding preliminary injunction, opinion and petition for rehearing, 1992 -- 1994; MS177.004.002.034.00025 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation - 1994, correspondence with opposing counsel, MS177.004.002.034.00026 (Box 34)
    - Marcos human rights litigation, pleadings regarding Sison v. Marcos, 1994; MS177.004.002.034.00027 (Box 34)
    - Government of Philippines appeal to 9th Circuit regarding preliminary injunction [1 of 2], 1994; MS177.004.002.034.00028 (Box 34)
    - Government of Philippines appeal to 9th Circuit regarding preliminary injunction [2 of 2], 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00001 (Box 35)
    - Proposal for human rights mission, 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00002 (Box 35)
    - Marcos: Substitution of plaintiffs, 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00003 (Box 35)
    - Marcos human rights litigation: correspondence among all plaintiffs counsel - privileged, 1994, MS177.004.002.035.00004 (Box 35)
    - Marcos human rights litigation: correspondence among Sison counsel and clients, (1994) - privileged [1 of 2], MS177.004.002.035.00005 (Box 35)
    - Marcos human rights litigation: correspondence among Sison counsel and clients, (1994) - privileged [2 of 2], MS177.004.002.035.00006 (Box 35)
    - [Class, 9th Circuit, supplemental excerpts of record], 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00007 (Box 35)
    - Marcos human rights litigation - pleadings [1 of 2], 1993 -- 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00008 (Box 35)
    - Marcos human rights litigation - pleadings [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00009 (Box 35)
    - Expert testimony for Marcos appeal, 1990 -- 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00010 (Box 35)
    - Marcos appeal - relation between actual and punitive damages, 1993 -- 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00011 (Box 35)
    - Plaintiffs work product - Sison, privileged [1 of 2], 1994 -- 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00012 (Box 35)
    - Plaintiffs work product - Sison, privileged [2 of 2], 1994 -- 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00013 (Box 35)
    - Individual plaintiffs - trial brief cases: work product: legal research for trial brief (compensatory damages trial), 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00014 (Box 35)
    - Individual plaintiffs - trial brief cases, 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00015 (Box 35)
    - Individual plaintiffs - trial brief cases: Lillich, damages for human rights violations in US courts, 1992; MS177.004.002.035.00016 (Box 35)
    - [James P. Linn declaration and memorandum], 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00017 (Box 35)
    - Swift's trial briefs, 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00018 (Box 35)
    - Narrative statement of Jim Jaranson, 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00019 (Box 35)
    - Trial exhibits for Dr. Jaranson, 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00020 (Box 35)
    - [Jaranson articles], 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00021 (Box 35)
    - Witness / exhibit lists, Sison / Piopongco plaintiffs, 1994; MS177.004.002.035.00022 (Box 35)
    - Special Master's report, 1994 -- 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00023 (Box 35)
    - Marcos damages trial transcript: Jan 1995, reporter's transcript, final pretrial conference, MS177.004.002.035.00024 (Box 35)
    - Marcos damages trial transcript: Jan 1995, Volume I, MS177.004.002.035.00025 (Box 35)
    - Marcos damages trial transcript: Jan 1995, Volumes II and III, MS177.004.002.035.00026 (Box 35)
    - Marcos damages trial transcript: Jan 1995, jury trial, MS177.004.002.035.00027 (Box 35)
    - Jurors, 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00028 (Box 35)
    - Jury instructions - direct action plaintiffs, 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00029 (Box 35)
    - Compensatory damages - trial brief of direct action plaintiffs, 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00030 (Box 35)
    - Verdicts regarding compensatory damages, 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00031 (Box 35)
    - M. Montes recommendations regarding present value, 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00032 (Box 35)
    - Direct action plaintiffs - proposed verdict forms, 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00033 (Box 35)
    - Compensatory damages - notes, 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00034 (Box 35)
    - Ely Piopongco testimony, 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00035 (Box 35)
    - Jan 1995 - Marcos human rights litigation: EL notes - damages trial, MS177.004.002.035.00036 (Box 35)
    - [Correspondence regarding compensatory damages trial], 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00037 (Box 35)
    - [Civil appeal instruction and notice of appeal], 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00038 (Box 35)
    - [Hilao v. Marcos - Plaintiffs-appellees' status report and motion to dismiss appeal], 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00039 (Box 35)
    - [Hilao v. Marcos - Plaintiffs-appellees emergency motion to dismiss appeal], 1995; MS177.004.002.035.00040 (Box 35)
    - Marcos post-trial hearings 1995, MS177.004.002.036.00001 (Box 36)
    - [Hilao v. Marcos - Response of Republic of the Philippines to emergency motion to dismiss appeal], 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00002 (Box 36)
    - Excerpts of record, Volume I - court records, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00003 (Box 36)
    - Excerpts of record, Volume II - court records, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00004 (Box 36)
    - Excerpts of record, Volume III - reporters' transcripts, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00005 (Box 36)
    - [Correspondence regarding appeals], 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00006 (Box 36)
    - [Hilao v. Marcos - Plaintiffs-appellees reply to letter of respondent-appellant regarding consolidation of appeals], 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00007 (Box 36)
    - [Hilao v. Marcos - brief of appellant, Republic of the Philippines], 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00008 (Box 36)
    - [Hilao v. Marcos - reply brief of appellant, Republic of the Philippines], 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00009 (Box 36)
    - Contempt proceedings, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00010 (Box 36)
    - [Motion for contempt], 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00011 (Box 36)
    - 9th Circuit rules, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00012 (Box 36)
    - Documents regarding settlement, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00013 (Box 36)
    - Substitution of Mark Lane for appeal, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00014 (Box 36)
    - Motion of defense counsel to withdrawal, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00015 (Box 36)
    - Intervenors, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00016 (Box 36)
    - Trial court final judgement - opinion / orders, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00017 (Box 36)
    - [Judgements], 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00018 (Box 36)
    - Hilao v. Marcos - appeal, excerpts of record, Volume 1 [1 of 2], 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00019 (Box 36)
    - Hilao v. Marcos - appeal, excerpts of record, Volume 1 [2 of 2], 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00020 (Box 36)
    - Hilao v. Marcos - appeal, excerpts of record, Volume 2, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00021 (Box 36)
    - Hilao v. Marcos - appeal (1995) [1 of 4]: Opening and reply brief for Imelda regarding injunction, MS177.004.002.036.00022 (Box 36)
    - Hilao v. Marcos - appeal (1995) [2 of 4]: Excert of record for Imelda regarding injunction, MS177.004.002.036.00023 (Box 36)
    - Hilao v. Marcos - appeal (1995) [3 of 4]: Excert of record for Imelda regarding injunction, MS177.004.002.036.00024 (Box 36)
    - Hilao v. Marcos - appeal (1995) [4 of 4]: Excert of record for Imelda regarding injunction, MS177.004.002.036.00025 (Box 36)
    - Transcript designations, 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00026 (Box 36)
    - Marcos human rights litigation - 1995: pleadings class action [1 of 3], MS177.004.002.036.00027 (Box 36)
    - Marcos human rights litigation - 1995: pleadings class action [2 of 3], MS177.004.002.036.00028 (Box 36)
    - Marcos human rights litigation - 1995: pleadings class action [3 of 3], MS177.004.002.036.00029 (Box 36)
    - [Damages research and notes], 1995; MS177.004.002.036.00030 (Box 36)
    - Marcos human rights litigation - 1995: pleadings Sison v. Marcos, MS177.004.002.036.00031 (Box 36)
    - Marcos human rights litigation - 1995: correspondence among plaintiffs' counsel, MS177.004.002.037.00001 (Box 37)
    - Marcos human rights litigation - 1995: correspondence among Sison counsel - privileged, MS177.004.002.037.00002 (Box 37)
    - Marcos human rights litigation - 1995: correspondence with opposing counsel, MS177.004.002.037.00003 (Box 37)
    - 1995 - Press regarding Marcos human rights litigation, MS177.004.002.037.00004 (Box 37)
    - [Hilao v. Marcos - appellant's excerpt of record, Republic of the Philippines], 1995; MS177.004.002.037.00005 (Box 37)
    - Sison - 9th Circuit [1 of 4]: 1996, MS177.004.002.037.00006 (Box 37)
    - Sison - 9th Circuit [2 of 4], 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00007 (Box 37)
    - Sison - 9th Circuit [3 of 4]: Transcript excerpts, 1992 -- 1995; MS177.004.002.037.00008 (Box 37)
    - Sison - 9th Circuit [4 of 4], 1995 -- 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00009 (Box 37)
    - Swift's cases, 9th Circuit [1 of 2], 1995 -- 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00010 (Box 37)
    - Swift's cases, 9th Circuit [2 of 2], 1995 -- 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00011 (Box 37)
    - Swiss bank proceedings, 1995 -- 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00012 (Box 37)
    - [Order confirming sale of Marcos Mercedes], 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00013 (Box 37)
    - [Sison briefs], 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00014 (Box 37)
    - [Jean-Pierre Garbade, Marcos estate representative], 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00015 (Box 37)
    - [LEI Investments motion], 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00016 (Box 37)
    - [Marcos estate petition for reconsideration, supplemental documents], 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00017 (Box 37)
    - [Supplemental relief motion and response], 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00018 (Box 37)
    - [Rosales / Narciso v. Credit Suisse / Swiss Bank Corporation], 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00019 (Box 37)
    - [Golden Budha Corporation appeal dismissal], 1996; MS177.004.002.037.00020 (Box 37)
    - Correspondence with Swiss banks on behalf of Sison / Piopongco plaintiffs (1995), 1995 -- 1997; MS177.004.002.037.00021 (Box 37)
    - Marcos timesheets, 1986 -- 1998; MS177.004.002.037.00022 (Box 37)
    - ACLU time sheets, 1987; MS177.004.002.037.00023 (Box 37)
    - Marcos human rights litigation expenses, 1995; MS177.004.002.037.00024 (Box 37)
    - Marcos current, 1997 -- 1998; MS177.004.002.037.00025 (Box 37)